You learn a lot about yourself when life
throws you curve balls. After my own
health scare, I've had to think about
what really matters. And for me, that's
family. Making life easier for you when
I'm gone. Isn't that right, D? And my
wife and kids, too. Obviously,
one way to plan ahead is with a
guaranteed over 50 plan from Sun Life,
the UK's most popular over 50s life
insurance.
That's even more popular than I was in
the 80s.
They guarantee a cash payout that your
premiums never rise. Plus, you'll be
accepted with no medical. You can choose
a plan to suit your budget with cover of
up to £18,000.
With Sun Life, you're helping to protect
your family's future.
Come on, girl. You want to take me for a
walk?
Don't wait. Call or search Sunlife Plan
today and get a free welcome gift card.